Ann-Felicity Mureithi: mnijibu
Norman Mwapea: Skia sentiments za gen alpha
Norman Mwapea: Kuhustle ka sjakosea. Ama ni aje Judith
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: @ stan wewe ebu confrim
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: aws
Norman Mwapea: Ati what tool did you use apart from gpt. That was just nasty
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: google search
William Arasirwa: chatgpt recieving shembeteng
Kitts Kikumu: units
Norman Mwapea: Nilidhani kuvisualize text using wi=ordcloud ndo text analysis. Boy was I wrong!!
Jeff Mogaka: mfuko
Jeff Mogaka: index 4 bana
Kitts Kikumu: money
Jeff Mogaka: chase the bag
Norman Mwapea: But is the bag aware we are chasing it
Norman Mwapea: Tafakari ya guka
Jeff Mogaka: @arasirwa unasema wewe hubag shawries ni bag gani hii unatumia
Alvin kipleting: bag of njugu
William Arasirwa: wewe umesahau unafanya mambo yako hadi unapea matress hickey @jeff
Norman Mwapea: Combination ya kutu na njaa inafanya mtu akue kitu
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: na si pycharm is outdated?
Jeff Mogaka: mucene
Jeff Mogaka: not yesterday
Alvin kipleting: @ jeff ptsd
Maureen Ngaire: Woishe Jeff, unaitwa Jeffrey?
Norman Mwapea: Josephine*
William Arasirwa: jeniffer
Maureen Ngaire: Hizo ni jina ya matress na wall
William Arasirwa: damn
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: Norman utashare nna sisi tuone
William Arasirwa: mkono ya left ni diana
Alvin kipleting: sukayo baka
Kitts Kikumu: Ei
William Arasirwa: ni mimi ama mwalimu is breaking and the screen is frozen?
Norman Mwapea: Nitawapatia
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: sawa Mwa-Pea
Maureen Ngaire: Apart from training Norman, what will be the goal. Azin what are you aiming to do?
Kitts Kikumu: wait is the data being loaded from an api
Norman Mwapea: I want to see the common words. Common topics. Who talks the most
Norman Mwapea: Etc etc
Maureen Ngaire: Wanene anajua hio
Norman Mwapea: pd.set_option("display.max_colwidth", None)
Norman Mwapea: Ati Oya, Mwalimu
Stanley Njihia: Siku moja nafaa niseme, oya boiz
Norman Mwapea: Kwani Crispus did analysis on our calls?
Norman Mwapea: Ama ulimaanisha nini Maureen
Kitts Kikumu: sentiment analysis tena mi bado niko bagging
Maureen Ngaire: hio ya pd options
William Arasirwa: nyinyi mnaona?
Alvin kipleting: yeah
William Arasirwa: eeh leo starlink wameniseti
Alvin kipleting: rada kwani
Alvin kipleting: toka meeting alafu urejoin
William Arasirwa: this is a fine example of human beings making life hard
William Arasirwa: now we are teaching an inanimate thing how to understand our language
Leon Wairachu: Tm alisema these things ni beginner friendly?
William Arasirwa: nakuambia string manipulation wewe
William Arasirwa: mtaitana
William Arasirwa: na hizo lambda
William Arasirwa: cha mkufuu mwana hu haa
Maureen Ngaire: na mayeng'
William Arasirwa: na hii akili ya jeff
William Arasirwa: hapa sitoboi
Kitts Kikumu: na bado tensors
William Arasirwa: tensors tunaweza pigana nazo
William Arasirwa: wewe unajua the way i hate string manipulation
Stanley Njihia: Kitts, si ii swali ulikua unataka kuuliza ata ushasahau?
Kitts Kikumu: acha amalize tu, its not that important
Maureen Ngaire: Sasa kama ya jana jeff ndio ilikua the most frequent word, but it was important. Sasa hio ni weakness ya tf-idf?
William Arasirwa: unataka kusema jeff is not important?
William Arasirwa: cold
Maureen Ngaire: Kwa context ya kile tunasoma the most frequent word is assigned a small value to show a lack of importance
William Arasirwa: eyy
William Arasirwa: ndiposa
Kitts Kikumu: I think ni kureduce redundancy
William Arasirwa: nini nini
Alvin kipleting: watu wa Tz wanaumia
Kitts Kikumu: save on memory, which ive actually noticed is a very important aspect of algorithms. We need results as quick as possible
Stanley Njihia: Mtu amwambie adelete everything
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: i was gonna say that
Maureen Ngaire: Njihia huwezi fanyia boiz wako ivo. That's very cold
Stanley Njihia: Niliskia wakisema you are colder
William Arasirwa: kikisii inaweza kuwa na stopwords @jeff?
Jeff Mogaka: hafanyi boiz wake poa
Norman Mwapea: Mnataka gani leo
Norman Mwapea: Kitu upbeat
Jeff Mogaka: white girl music
Alvin kipleting: eka yeat
Maureen Ngaire: Judith alikataa ile ya jana ya watu wazee
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: alvin nilikwambia hizo uskize ukiwa pekee yako
Jeff Mogaka: @alvin niiiiceee
Norman Mwapea: Judith ni gen z
Norman Mwapea: ?
Jeff Mogaka: eka yeat alafu umalizie na playboi carti
Nesphory Mwadime: Yes
Jeff Mogaka: yeah @ norman
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: wekeeni arasirwa songs
Norman Mwapea: Mnataka kina Wesley wakimbie
Jeff Mogaka: Judioth ni genz
William Arasirwa: hamskizagi okello max?
William Arasirwa: taya
Jeff Mogaka: *Judith
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: somebody recap
Jeff Mogaka: eka yeat bana
Jeff Mogaka: ama hizo wimbo za arasirwa
Jeff Mogaka: ama mtu arecap hii NLP index 0
Jeff Mogaka: next breathe by yeat bana
Kitts Kikumu: jeff music taste yako ni tiktok
Jeff Mogaka: @kitts ziiii man wtf
Stanley Njihia: Huldah awa watu wanakufukuza sio?
Jeff Mogaka: lol
Jeff Mogaka: Norman unaplay wimbo za devo bana
Alvin kipleting: @ arasirwa ati mapenzi yashakudhulumu maisha haya cinema
Maureen Ngaire: Nishawai skia izi wimbo kwa nganya
William Arasirwa: maureen uko sure unatoshea kwa kiti ya mat?
Huldah Rotich: Hehehehe ati wananifukuza. Yho....I am right at home.
Jeff Mogaka: mlango ya mat hadi
Norman Mwapea: Anakalia seat tatu za kule nyuma
Alvin kipleting: eka tonka
Norman Mwapea: Hii yeat yenu ni gani
William Arasirwa: mnasema maureen anatatembea kama hotair ballon?
Jeff Mogaka: merimela
Maureen Ngaire: Ata siwezi jump into conclusions
Alvin kipleting: merimela ni goated
Alvin kipleting: eeii
William Arasirwa: you bounce into conclusions
Norman Mwapea: Ona vile Judith anafurahi. Baby boomers wanafurahi
Jeff Mogaka: naona mmeeka stuff za Judith
Alvin kipleting: say what now
Maureen Ngaire: Wlliam kizungu si ngumu ivo, hio uliskia wapi?
Judith Otieno: Norman ni kwa kutuchezea yeat
Alvin kipleting: @ norman rada ya tarzan
Norman Mwapea: Caught red handed. Haikua Yeat hio
Norman Mwapea: Nimekumulika
Judith Otieno: Si fahamu hawa
Norman Mwapea: Ah wapi na najua saii unamoonwalk Judith
Alvin kipleting: eka sky
Maureen Ngaire: tuekee digidigi majimaji ........this way that way .......
Norman Mwapea: Nani ameimba sky
Huldah Rotich: Anyone going for the Kulture concert on Sato? Millenials in the house
Alvin kipleting: playboi
Judith Otieno: Na William asked for Okello Max kama Dj didnt see
Alvin kipleting: taya ni therapy ya @william
Fridah Njung'e: DJ Normie!!!! 🎉🎉💥💥🎉🎉
Jeff Mogaka: Jonte amerudi
Fridah Njung'e: For now 🤭
William Arasirwa: you guys are mental
Huldah Rotich: DJ Normie leo umeweza sana
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: word cloud is pretty
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: it will be big
Jeff Mogaka: more weight is diabolical
Jeff Mogaka: relatable
William Arasirwa: vitaa
William Arasirwa: jeff you bad human
Jeff Mogaka: usisahau boiz
Jeff Mogaka: @arasirwa me innocently denying the allegations
Norman Mwapea: Unacompete na uliloose
Norman Mwapea: Sad
Maureen Ngaire: Bert
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: wewe hukua @ norman
Norman Mwapea: Fununu zilinifikia
William Arasirwa: nini mbaya
Kitts Kikumu: fununu kwa rununu
Norman Mwapea: Walete kati
William Arasirwa: nakuambia phase four has sent us to the abyss of content, models na processes kaa wan billion
William Arasirwa: nothing beats finance tho
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: autocorrection on whatsapp ? is that nlp /
William Arasirwa: au vipi @crispus na @stan
Stanley Njihia: Ii masakhane sio jina ya kiluhya though?
William Okomba: https://www.masakhane.io/
William Arasirwa: auto correction has been there ata kwa word @ann
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: is it nlp?
Norman Mwapea: Yes Ann, it is!!
William Arasirwa: depends with how you approach it but its nlp anyway
Norman Mwapea: Remember NLP by definition is application of language, linguistics and CS
Norman Mwapea: In computers
William Arasirwa: nlp na string manipulation ata heri stats
Alvin kipleting: uko na one year
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: mine will die
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: its struggling now it will die
William Arasirwa: heri stats
Leon Wairachu: Mine died and resurrected
William Arasirwa: mimi nifunze kombyuta sheng?
Jeff Mogaka: nifanye tu nlp hivi napata mistari....ama natengeneza model ya mistari
William Arasirwa: cannot be me
Kitts Kikumu: is it a bird is it a plane? No its your laptop
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: duo lingo using nlp?
William Arasirwa: ***ann asking a question: gari ni car in english
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: im thinking out loud
William Arasirwa: you have a mute button?
Alvin kipleting: eiii hii vita yote acha tublame nlp
Kitts Kikumu: Ei
Stanley Njihia: wueeh
Norman Mwapea: isnt this in clutering
Stanley Njihia: Arasirwa umesema izo inner thoughts zibaki ndani?
William Arasirwa: na vile ann ni kadogo, saying that ni kama uweke walkie talkie kwa gunia
Stanley Njihia: Eeiyy
William Arasirwa: if ann was an apple product she'd be the ipod
Alvin kipleting: @ Arasirwa who hurt you
Maureen Ngaire: wueeeeeh
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: @ Arasirwa unatka nishuke na wewe kweli?
William Arasirwa: kushuka na ukobelow sea level?
Stanley Njihia: var checking
Alvin kipleting: mnaenda wapi
Maureen Ngaire: shuka na yeye amesema wewe ni kadogo
William Arasirwa: mnapenda vita
Kitts Kikumu: arasirwa is just throwing hands today
William Arasirwa: talking about tokenization and ann is a human token anyway
Alvin kipleting: eiii
Maureen Ngaire: Oneni vile Kipleting anafurahia akiona vita
William Arasirwa: jeff is awkwardly silent or he is performing his rituals?
Jeff Mogaka: pona kwanza moyo
William Arasirwa: utakuja kupata muscle pull kwa mkono
William Arasirwa: ukona deep heat?
William Arasirwa: or there is nothing hot in your house?
Maureen Ngaire: Rituals ni za nyakati za usiku usiku
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: @ arasirwa unacompensate 👀👀
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: you know
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: tall on the outside
Maureen Ngaire: Ouch!
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: short in common sense etc ......
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: and others but tunaelewa
William Arasirwa: well common sense was never common
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: ndio unacompensate
Alvin kipleting: get ready get ready
Jeff Mogaka: @ngaire did you just dj afro
William Arasirwa: you can do better ama you are also short on thoughts?
Maureen Ngaire: Ann huwezi shuka na Arasirwa na bafo ukue shy. Pick one!
Maureen Ngaire: *bado
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: and you tall on nonsense .....
William Arasirwa: msm sasa mimi nimefanya nini
Alvin kipleting: @ jeff maureen amesema wewe ndio staring kwenye horacinema
Kitts Kikumu: ive seen a couple of ones
Maureen Ngaire: Jeff sitaki usherati
William Arasirwa: yes
William Arasirwa: nlp ni string manipulation tupu
Jeff Mogaka: @ngaire usherati tena
Jeff Mogaka: boiz
Jeff Mogaka: mmesema Ann akue tu house wife
William Arasirwa: hio sawa sawa ni hafifu @ stan
Kitts Kikumu: no shortcuts
Jeff Mogaka: heeeh
Jeff Mogaka: damn
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: @ Jeff unataka nije kwako pia
Stanley Njihia: Ann unasema you are not yet entertained?
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: vayoooooleeeens!!1
Jeff Mogaka: ann haezi nishtua...saa do mbilikimos look scary
Ann-Felicity Mureithi: @ Jeff , you get terrified by baby girls , like 3 month babies
Jeff Mogaka: ever since you were born hujai look down upon anyone like literally looking down just looking up to people
William Arasirwa: ann puttion on santa clothes makes her look like a gnome
William Arasirwa: putting
Jeff Mogaka: ankle socks za Leon inajaa mguu ya ann vibaya sana
William Arasirwa: ei
Maureen Ngaire: mko kinky uku, Ann unataka kwenda kuona Jeff
Norman Mwapea: What!!
Jeff Mogaka: @ngaire sitaki watu wafikirie nikona mtoto and I'm young